

SURIYA KHUNTA SOFTWARE TESTER/ QA

CONTACT



097-326-0054



suriya_khunta@hotmail.com



50/2 Lat Krabang, Lat Krabang, Bangkok, 10520 Thailand

EDUCATION

High School (2016-2019)

Padeng vittaya School Education Program : Science - Math | GPA : 3.45

University (2019-2023)

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang.

Degree: Bachelor of Science in Industrial Education

Major: Engineering Education | GPA: 3.06

LANGUAGE

English

Thai

ABOUT ME

Deadline - oriented software tester with over one years of experience writing test script , test case and implementing automation tests to help applications and web app run smoothly.

Collaborates with software team in continuous build and deployment process. Excellent learning in new software tools and best practices in software quality assurance

EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

Nawamintrachuthit Vocational Education College

Student Teacher

Responsibility: Teach high school students computer science.

May 2023 - October 2023

Vgenz Company Limited

Software tester, Support, Implement

Responsibility : Manual Testing Mobile Application & Web App , Train & Support Customer in program

November 2023 - Present

Siam Commercial Bank PCL (Contract)

Test Executor (New OEF)

Responsibility: Manual testing web application, check data update in SQL, Review test case for users in meetings, Writing test plan, test script for testing

SKILL

Hard Skill:

- Python
- MS Office
- Java Script
- Visual Code
- Postman
- My SQL, My SQL Server

Traning Skill:

- Postman & Newman For API Testing
- Cypress For Automation Testing
- Robot Framework (Selenium Library)

Tools:

- lira
- Trello